makli.com 2011-01-02

# Privacy Policy

Browse >

[Home](http://www.makli.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

## Log Files

Makli.com only collect segregated data for the use of analytic purposes; we do not save or collect personal information about the visitors and users. Makli.com only gathers non-personal data information such as browser type, IP Address location, and news’s visited by the user, referring website, date and time spent by the user on our website. All above explained information data is used by Makli.com to increase the performance and functionality of the website.

## Private and Third Party Cookies

Makli.com use cookies systems as it is easy to collect information about the visitor’s performance through cookies. Only information sent by the user using the web browser has stored in the cookies.

Makli.com served by Google and other third party vendor cookies; these other vendors including Google use cookies system, known as DART cookies that enable these vendors to place advertisement on Makli.com. Some vendors use Java Scripts to place Advertisement on our site. For DART cookies and privacy Policy please visit Google Privacy Policy at  
<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Please note that Makli.com Privacy Policy does not apply on any of the advertisements on our site, if you want any more detail about the Privacy policies of our advertisers please consult with their respective Policies. Any individual can disable/block cookies for their personal browsers any time, to disable cookies of that respective website please consult to that specific browser options.

## Contact Us

Any individual can contact Makli.com if he/she has any question(s) / problem(s) regarding our Privacy Policy and terms and conditions.

We are reachable through contact us form at  
<http://www.makli.com/contact/>

## Privacy Policy Reviews

Makli.com reserves the rights to alter/replace or update any point of their Privacy Policy at any time without prior information to the user. It is recommended that you keep on checking our Privacy Policy periodically in order to stay update. Any Individuals continuous visit(s) to Makli.com will mean that they agree to our upgraded/changes Privacy Policy(s).
